{
    "id": "952554c20d4e43df9057f8d05aa0781f",
    "title": "Infinitives And Ing Forms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I hate the idea …………………………. old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "of getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43dd7f3437b54a5d9e368b251795c64b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thought ……………………….. never entered his head.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to fail",
                "of failing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "45ca135fafaa4b68bceefbecd960b4a8"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very good ………………………. problems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to solve",
                "at solve",
                "at solving"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "20b14432f9cc4e91a6f5277a29b756f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired …………………………. to advice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to listen",
                "of listening"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3990e0ed644f4eb6875e60be4a9e0165"
        },
        {
            "question": "A strimmer is a machine ………………………….. grass and weeds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to cut",
                "for cutting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9a5ea042f2ef48d2be45c2de1f784e44"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must find something ………………………. that fly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to kill",
                "for killing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a4f5af7086b4055b6e1f5af56515419"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am proud …………………………… won.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of having",
                "to have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "075000caf13e4e3c902d01e949e868b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t make an omelette without …………………….. eggs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to break",
                "breaking",
                "to breaking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7612a41dd6a24ad99e79e36f6bb7efd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward to ……………………………… from you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0fa28ae31fc64992bfef34385f111638"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used to ……………………………. in London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "drive",
                "driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b86abe5924c24519af57bc16e3dc2170"
        }
    ]
}